{
    "subject": "resource/Faiz_Ahmad_Faiz",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Ghazal",
    "human_readable": "The genre of Faiz Ahmad Faiz's work is Ghazal.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7660109996795654,
            "question": "Is Faiz Ahmad Faiz known for writing sonnets or ghazals?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7244868278503418,
            "question": "What literary genre is Faiz Ahmad Faiz known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7149473428726196,
            "question": "How is Faiz Ahmad Faiz's work categorized in terms of literary genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6692654490470886,
            "question": "Faiz Ahmad Faiz's work belongs to which literary tradition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5182523131370544,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Ghazal poetry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3964169919490814,
            "question": "What is the characteristic structure of a Ghazal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38157185912132263,
            "question": "Faiz Ahmad Faiz's poetry predominantly uses which poetic form?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31519341468811035,
            "question": "Give an example of a form of poetry associated with Faiz Ahmad Faiz."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3042159676551819,
            "question": "Can you name a famous poet who wrote in the Ghazal form?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2789686620235443,
            "question": "What type of poetry did Faiz Ahmad Faiz write?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The genre of Faiz Ahmad Faiz's work is Ghazal.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8718_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a famous poet who wrote in the Ghazal form?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8718_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of a form of poetry associated with Faiz Ahmad Faiz.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8718_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Faiz Ahmad Faiz's poetry predominantly uses which poetic form?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8718_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8718_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8718_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8718_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8718_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8718_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8718_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8718_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8718_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8718_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8718_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. Specifically, document 1.txt states that Faiz Ahmad Faiz was a renowned Pakistani poet who wrote in the Urdu language, and his works are known for their progressive and humanist themes, as well as their revolutionary spirit. Document 11.txt also mentions that Faiz's genres include Ghazal. Therefore, the triple \"The genre of Faiz Ahmad Faiz's work is Ghazal\" is correct according to the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents indicate that Faiz Ahmad Faiz wrote ghazals, among other poetic forms. For instance, the document states, \"Faiz, on the other hand, though he is equally good in his ghazals, has a place of pre eminence in Urdu poetry because of nazms.\" This supports the query that the genre of Faiz Ahmad Faiz's work includes Ghazal."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}